

Jesús Liendo

Web Developer



+52 87 13 37 90 77



jesusliendo55@gmail.com



<u>_inkedIn</u>



Gómez Palacio, DGO. México

EXPERIENCE

March 2023 – Present

Developer Semi SR - Angular

Lumston

Development of web applications, use libraries, templates and responsive chatbots, implementation of versioning and improvements in scalable projects.

January 2020 – March 2023

Web Developer - Angular

soliduSystems

Develop large scale web pages using angular, css, html, typescript, be responsive, clean code and good design. Integration with billing and migration from version 3.3 to 4.0. Structuring of folders in Angular and documentation of functionality of components, services, directives and interfaces.

January 2020 – December 2020

FullStack - Laravel

soliduSvstems

Website development using local database in mysql, using blade with html, css, vue, ajax and boostrap.

Manager Systems

January 2016 – December 2019

Secucore

Attend the five brenches by teamviewer or by telephone, preventive and corrective maintenances of computer equipament, development in VB6, use SqlServe, c#, api mercadolibre and billing migration from version 3.2 to 3.3.

EDUCATION Information Tecnology

Universidad Politecnica de Gómez Palacio Dgo

2012- 2015 Graduated

September - 2012 to Dicember -2015

REFERENCES

Marilu Romero
Software Engineer
+52 87 11 07 48 73
Romeromarilu13@gmail.com

Pepe Flores Software Engineer +52 87 17 68 03 38 pepefloressalas@gmail.com

STATEMENT

Web developer specialized in experienced Frontend development with all the stages of development cycle of dynamic web projects with numerous programming languages including Javascript, MySql, Adonis JS, Laravel, Vue and Angular.

My main functions are deliver my tasks in time and from analiyze the requirements of each to project and corresponding tasks to deliver.

SKILLS

Professional

HTML	
CSS	
Highly responsible and reliable	
Angular	
JavaScript	
Personal	

Courses

Creativity

Hard Work

Communication

Angular, Udemy May – 2022 to Jul - 2022 Laravel, Udemy Aug – 2018 to Oct - 2018